dnsmadeeasy.com 2010-01-10

# Free DNS, DNS, DDNS, Reliable DNS, Free Redirection, Cheap DNS - DNS MADE EASY

Privacy Policy

DNS Made Easy takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.**

What this Privacy Policy Covers  

  * This Privacy Policy covers DNS Made Easy's treatment of personally identifiable information that DNS Made Easy collects when you are on the DNS Made Easy site, and when you use DNS Made Easy's services. This policy also covers DNS Made Easy's treatment of any personally identifiable information that DNS Made Easy's business partners share with DNS Made Easy or that DNS Made Easy may collect on a partner's site. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DNS Made Easy does not own or control, or to people that DNS Made Easy does not employ or manage or to sites using DNS Made Easy's subdomain solution. 

Information Collection and Use  

  * DNS Made Easy collects personally identifiable information when you register for a DNS Made Easy account, when you use certain DNS Made Easy products or services, and when you visit DNS Made Easy pages. DNS Made Easy may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 
  * When you register with DNS Made Easy, we ask for your name, email address, zip code, and business or industry. Once you register with DNS Made Easy and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * DNS Made Easy also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address. 
  * DNS Made Easy uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure  

  * DNS Made Easy will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 
  * You agree that DNS Made Easy / Tiggee may use Your name and logo in presentations, marketing materials, customer lists, financial reports, Web site listings of customers, Search Results Pages, and Referral Pages. 
  * DNS Made Easy may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of DNS Made Easy to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or 
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the DNS Made Easy Warranty and Disclaimer, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Choices users have regarding the collected information.**  

  * Since DNS Made Easy relies on the personal information to label your information for security, it is impossible for users to "opt-out" of the information tracking. You could just not use the service. 

Cookies  

  * DNS Made Easy may set and access DNS Made Easy cookies on your computer. 
  * DNS Made Easy allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to DNS Made Easy's cookies. 

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences  

  * DNS Made Easy gives you the ability to edit your DNS Made Easy Account Information and preferences at any time, with exception to your email. 
  * All users issues are resolved by email. You can email any issue to [support@dnsmadeeasy.com](mailto:support@dnsmadeeasy.com). 

Security  

  * Your DNS Made Easy Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 
  * In certain areas DNS Made Easy may use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 
  * All information is stored in DNS Made Easy databases which are password protected to protect your data from unauthorized employee access. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy  

  * DNS Made Easy may amend this policy from time to time. All users should review this page regularly. 

Spam  

  * We personally do not like spam and we will do nothing with your data to have spam sent to you. However DNS Made Easy may from time to time send you an email indicating the new services / products that DNS Made Easy is providing or that Tiggee is providing. Tiggee owns DNS Made Easy and all of it's services. 

Questions or Suggestions  

  * If you have questions or suggestions contact [support@dnsmadeeasy.com](mailto:support@dnsmadeeasy.com).
